rentown.net 2018-01-14

# Privacy Policy - RentOwn.net

**Effective: January 8, 2013**

RentOwn.net is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. By accessing our Web site or using our services, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

**_Collection and Use of Information_**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you, specifically your name, e-mail address, payment method, telephone number, postal address, as well as other information when such information is combined with your personal information. We collect and use your personally identifiable information to give you better customer service and to provide you with convenient access to our products and services.

We also use your personally identifiable information to keep you up to date on the latest products, newsletters, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. We may also use your personally identifiable information to contact you to participate in market research, so that we can gauge your satisfaction and continually improve our products and service. Out of respect for your privacy; we give you the option to not receive these types of communications. If you do not wish to receive our promotional material you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link. Additionally, you may instruct us to remove your information from the customer lists which we distribute to our advertisers and other third party marketers.

**_Links to Other Sites_**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by RentOwn.net. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**_Cookies and Automatically Collected Information_**

As you browse the RentOwn.net site, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive for record keeping purposes. In general, cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you may not be able to use the RentOwn.net site or service.

We use other technologies, including pixel tags, to gather information on how our users interact with our site and to othewise help us efficiently operate and monitor our site and service. These technologies, show us, for example, conversion rates, click-throughs and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our site and our service. Third parties, including consultants we engage and online advertisers, may also use this technology to perform similar services for us as well as to assess their own advertising or services.

**_Security_**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**_Disclosure of Personal Information_**

We use other reputable companies, agents or contractors to perform services on our behalf. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your personal information. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them.

RentOwn.net also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law or if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights. In the event that RentOwn.net is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right, to sell or otherwise transfer the personal information we have collected as part of that transaction provided that such third party continues to honor our privacy policy.

**_Contact_**

Effective: January 8, 2013

If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please [contact us](mailto:info@rentown.net).
